==========
7e79357d-a903-4b7d-9070-068c2419e7ec
2.2 Radio Wave Propagation
==========
{"TopicId": "7e79357d-a903-4b7d-9070-068c2419e7ec", "QuestionId": "977606cf-ddcd-4f3d-a32f-bcd32fa859d9", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 9", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.721902", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "977606cf-ddcd-4f3d-a32f-bcd32fa859d9", "TopicId": "7e79357d-a903-4b7d-9070-068c2419e7ec", "SyllabusRef": "2.2.2", "Question": "How can VHF transmission and reception range be improved?", "Answer": "By climbing to a higher altitude.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.721832", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "7e79357d-a903-4b7d-9070-068c2419e7ec", "QuestionId": "bc6fbfc2-6144-4892-a62b-cc38c792e9e5", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 9", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722028", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "bc6fbfc2-6144-4892-a62b-cc38c792e9e5", "TopicId": "7e79357d-a903-4b7d-9070-068c2419e7ec", "SyllabusRef": "2.2.2", "Question": "Which characteristic of the HF band allows for greater transmission and reception range?", "Answer": "Sky waves.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722002", "Type": "q"}



==

{"QuestionId": "4ec47fee-0db5-4209-801c-0c12e8b1b8f6", "TopicId": "68abba26-615d-4249-a02e-64572c5a058a", "SyllabusRef": "2.4.2", "Question": "If after turning the VHF radio on a continuous loud static is heard through the aircraft speaker, what should the pilot do?", "Answer": "Turn the squelch control down.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722672", "Type": "q"}

{"QuestionId": "4ec47fee-0db5-4209-801c-0c12e8b1b8f6", "TopicId": "68abba26-615d-4249-a02e-64572c5a058a", "SyllabusRef": "2.4.2", "Question": "If after turning the VHF radio on a continuous loud static is heard through the aircraft speaker, what should the pilot do?", "Answer": "Turn the squelch control down.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722672", "Type": "q"}

==========
bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a
2.6 SSR Transponders
==========

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "fd05854d-7861-455e-94ba-8f02adeb38ba", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722789", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "fd05854d-7861-455e-94ba-8f02adeb38ba", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.4", "Question": "What function should be selected on a typical transponder to transmit Mode A?", "Answer": "ON.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722769", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "c9a83fbf-5800-40ee-821c-6b1260d13600", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722868", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c9a83fbf-5800-40ee-821c-6b1260d13600", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.2", "Question": "A radar controller gives an aircraft the following instructions \"Alfa Bravo Charlie, Stop Squawking Charlie - Wrong Indication\".  What action does the radar controller require the pilot to take?", "Answer": "De-select Mode C.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722841", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "1a2aebd1-2d0f-458b-a849-3e6da2c6f2f6", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722925", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "1a2aebd1-2d0f-458b-a849-3e6da2c6f2f6", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.2", "Question": "Most aircraft transponders have a function switch with five functions.  What are they?", "Answer": "Off, Standby, On, Alt and Test.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722903", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "42bec6b6-ab1d-4384-8c8a-08a746a1ceda", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722979", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "42bec6b6-ab1d-4384-8c8a-08a746a1ceda", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.4", "Question": "What information will Mode A send to the radar controller?", "Answer": "Position information and identification.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.722958", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "4703ad9c-0503-41ae-a6d0-6371dafc8b0a", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723036", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "4703ad9c-0503-41ae-a6d0-6371dafc8b0a", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.4", "Question": "What information will Mode C (Alt) send to the radar controller?", "Answer": "Position information, altitude information and identification.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723013", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "3be7263d-f209-4db3-9f02-80252aed7318", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723095", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "3be7263d-f209-4db3-9f02-80252aed7318", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.8", "Question": "When asked by the controller to \"SQUAWK IDENT\", what does the pilot need to do?", "Answer": \"Press and release the "ident" button on the transponder, no verbal response is required.\", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723071", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "0723700e-5b29-4ce1-a39a-efd47c71e030", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723148", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "0723700e-5b29-4ce1-a39a-efd47c71e030", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.6", "Question": "In an emergency, what transponder code should be set.", "Answer": "7700.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723129", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "7e9b7bcd-7ea9-49d4-851d-f7857b0ccf5b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723214", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "7e9b7bcd-7ea9-49d4-851d-f7857b0ccf5b", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.6", "Question": "What transponder code should be set in the event of unlawful interference?", "Answer": "7500.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723193", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "1da7cd7b-79b9-4927-b139-a8c4ece5ff6b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723265", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "1da7cd7b-79b9-4927-b139-a8c4ece5ff6b", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.6", "Question": "What transponder code should be set in the event of communications failure?", "Answer": "7600.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723245", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "37083026-acf2-44b1-8ce7-44da6a302a7a", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 6", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723320", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "37083026-acf2-44b1-8ce7-44da6a302a7a", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.8", "Question": "What does it mean when ATC ask an aircraft to \"SQUAWK CHARLIE\"?", "Answer": "Set Mode C or Alt on the transponder.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723297", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "cb43862f-1652-4c5d-aa8a-237bcd3f11c5", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 6", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723374", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "cb43862f-1652-4c5d-aa8a-237bcd3f11c5", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.2", "Question": "What transponder code should be set when operating in the circuit at a controlled aerodrome?", "Answer": "2200.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723353", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "d57ab51f-3cd3-4a81-85df-53bfbb55818f", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 6", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723437", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "d57ab51f-3cd3-4a81-85df-53bfbb55818f", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.8", "Question": "What does it mean when ATC ask an aircraft to \"RESET SQUAWK\"?", "Answer": "The controller wants the pilot to reset the assigned squawk code on the transponder.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723413", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "3aa6bfe2-f950-4a01-8d48-742b26ac6ce3", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 6", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723494", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "3aa6bfe2-f950-4a01-8d48-742b26ac6ce3", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.8", "Question": "ATC tells an aircraft to \"SQUAWK STANDBY\", what should the pilot do?", "Answer": \"Select the "STBY" function on the transponder.\", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723471", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "c1fc126e-7051-4c20-9b3d-15315b6b894e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723546", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c1fc126e-7051-4c20-9b3d-15315b6b894e", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.2", "Question": "What transponder code must be set when operating in the circuit at an uncontrolled aerodrome?", "Answer": "1200.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723526", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "c44f7be4-07f2-43bf-8036-01e57959b13b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723613", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c44f7be4-07f2-43bf-8036-01e57959b13b", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.2", "Question": "Helicopters operating under VFR should set which transponder code?", "Answer": "1500.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723593", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "098bfee9-c9a4-4216-817e-fdd0b8adfc5a", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723673", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "098bfee9-c9a4-4216-817e-fdd0b8adfc5a", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.12", "Question": "Under what conditions is an aircraft able to operate in transponder mandatory airspace without an operable transponder?", "Answer": "Only with specific authorisation from the ATC unit controlling the airspace.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723648", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "709dabed-a03d-4aae-94e4-d207ab6fd936", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723730", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "709dabed-a03d-4aae-94e4-d207ab6fd936", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.12", "Question": "If the transponder failures, is the pilot required to notify anyone?", "Answer": "Yes, immediately notify the ATC unit controlling the airspace.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723707", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "QuestionId": "183342a2-8d71-48b8-9467-589c11df056b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723785", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "183342a2-8d71-48b8-9467-589c11df056b", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.8", "Question": "Is it necessary for all the aircraft in a formation flight to operate a transponder?", "Answer": "No, unless otherwise instructed by ATC.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723763", "Type": "q"}

--- DONE UP TO HERE ---


==========
6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5
2.8 Emergency Locator Transmitter(ELT)
==========
{"QuestionId": "183342a2-8d71-48b8-9467-589c11df056b", "TopicId": "bedadc0e-e29d-4685-bfd8-caee35a2d80a", "SyllabusRef": "2.6.8", "Question": "Is it necessary for all the aircraft in a formation flight to operate a transponder?", "Answer": "No, unless otherwise instructed by ATC.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723763", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "d28b9c0a-77c6-4e89-90f8-581a78824bfb", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723906", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "d28b9c0a-77c6-4e89-90f8-581a78824bfb", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.2", "Question": "On what frequencies does an ELT transmit?", "Answer": "121.5 MHz and 406MHz.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723884", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "2c800c27-6062-49a3-8495-fbfa796cc844", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723959", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "2c800c27-6062-49a3-8495-fbfa796cc844", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.4", "Question": "Does a manned free balloon have to carry an ELT?", "Answer": "No.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.723940", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "d8008391-21b2-42f8-98c4-cc4685c11e7d", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724029", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "d8008391-21b2-42f8-98c4-cc4685c11e7d", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.6", "Question": "When will an automatic ELT be activated?", "Answer": "When a given rate of deceleration is experienced.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724007", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "57ae5f70-f66c-4d3a-abce-6de992dca36f", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724095", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "57ae5f70-f66c-4d3a-abce-6de992dca36f", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.6", "Question": "Can the ELT be manually activated?", "Answer": "Yes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724076", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "32e86548-acc5-4962-8eb7-19dc8dcb919f", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724157", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "32e86548-acc5-4962-8eb7-19dc8dcb919f", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.8", "Question": "How long will the ELT battery last for if it is not used?", "Answer": "Five years.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724127", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "dcf27376-6aa9-4dcf-9e0d-ffc34314bcae", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724230", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "dcf27376-6aa9-4dcf-9e0d-ffc34314bcae", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.8", "Question": \"Do ELT systems have their own power source, or do they use the aircraft"s electrical systems for operation?\", "Answer": \"ELT"s have internal battery/batteries, and operate independent of the aircraft electrical system.\", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724193", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "345298b1-fcab-48ed-9fa2-ed4980bb978e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724297", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "345298b1-fcab-48ed-9fa2-ed4980bb978e", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.8", "Question": "Your ELT was used intermittently for a total of one hour, are you required to replace the battery?", "Answer": "Yes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724276", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "59b47f61-8592-4678-8863-d125a9a0aba5", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724373", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "59b47f61-8592-4678-8863-d125a9a0aba5", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.8", "Question": "In the event of an emergency, to which position must the ELT remote switch be selected?", "Answer": "\"ON\".", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724343", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "2ba88553-042c-4dfb-be0e-8f02ba92b317", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724447", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "2ba88553-042c-4dfb-be0e-8f02ba92b317", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.8", "Question": "If the ELT\"s remote switch is selected to \"ARM\", how will the ELT be activated?", "Answer": "At a specific rate of deceleration (\"g\" switch\") during an accident or hard landing.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724408", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "984b293c-43f7-47a4-89b3-304eee17c31f", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724513", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "984b293c-43f7-47a4-89b3-304eee17c31f", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.10", "Question": "When may an ELT be tested?", "Answer": "During the first 5 minutes after the hour, for a maximum of three audio sweeps.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724490", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "02e73d58-2a16-44fd-a1c1-ec4884727d48", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724566", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "02e73d58-2a16-44fd-a1c1-ec4884727d48", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.4", "Question": "If you carry a portable ELT, does the aircraft still require an ELT to be installed before you go flying?", "Answer": "No.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724546", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "7fbd19d6-c9fe-4b18-9176-7a6f59a9237e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724642", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "7fbd19d6-c9fe-4b18-9176-7a6f59a9237e", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.4", "Question": "You plan a flight in a microlight aircraft with only two seats and operating within 10nm from where you departed.  Do you require an ELT?", "Answer": "No.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724601", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "62bab912-8b90-4c62-94e4-bb52af3bf10e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724699", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "62bab912-8b90-4c62-94e4-bb52af3bf10e", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.10", "Question": "Are you allowed to self test your ELT in flight?", "Answer": "No.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724681", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "QuestionId": "0490dd2e-9a29-44af-888a-d937228b8db9", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724762", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "0490dd2e-9a29-44af-888a-d937228b8db9", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.12", "Question": "If You suspect your ELT has been activated after a hard landing, what should your actions be?", "Answer": "Check 121.5 for an ELT signal.  If a signal is heard, hold the switch to \"ON\" for no more than 5 seconds, then switch back to \"ARM\".  Contact ATC and RCCNZ asap.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724732", "Type": "q"}

==========
0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c
2.10 Practices and Rules.
==========
{"QuestionId": "0490dd2e-9a29-44af-888a-d937228b8db9", "TopicId": "6b0ecf05-d057-4669-bb26-71c974c5fdc5", "SyllabusRef": "2.8.12", "Question": "If You suspect your ELT has been activated after a hard landing, what should your actions be?", "Answer": "Check 121.5 for an ELT signal.  If a signal is heard, hold the switch to \"ON\" for no more than 5 seconds, then switch back to \"ARM\".  Contact ATC and RCCNZ asap.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724732", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "f62adaa8-e8c1-420d-9d31-58ac4c8ac915", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724858", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "f62adaa8-e8c1-420d-9d31-58ac4c8ac915", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": "Which language must you use when making a radio call?", "Answer": "English.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724838", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "0fd019fe-fe03-4635-9410-bd1f709bb8cf", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724909", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "0fd019fe-fe03-4635-9410-bd1f709bb8cf", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": "The time is 0934.  How will you transmit this time?", "Answer": "Tree Fower.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724890", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "501b8c60-ec0f-48c0-ba7b-370e496d8248", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724961", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "501b8c60-ec0f-48c0-ba7b-370e496d8248", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": \"Are you allowed to use plain language if you don"t know or have forgotten the correct phraseology?\", "Answer": "Yes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724941", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "a1be8b81-cb2e-450a-98b4-9472047aea73", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725012", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "a1be8b81-cb2e-450a-98b4-9472047aea73", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": "When giving altitude information, is it necessary for each number to be spoken individually?", "Answer": "No.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.724993", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "e08cc252-daab-43cb-a081-8c109ca4da38", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725064", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "e08cc252-daab-43cb-a081-8c109ca4da38", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": "How should you respond if you receive a clearance or instruction that you cannot comply with?", "Answer": \"Use the phrase "UNABLE" and give a reason.\", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725042", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "9e2c4ad9-beee-45f2-94cb-d0790cdd44fd", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725114", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "9e2c4ad9-beee-45f2-94cb-d0790cdd44fd", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "Where is UNICOM available?", "Answer": "At some unattended aerodromes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725095", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "4b3283a2-0ab7-41d3-99f2-d9d20bc08319", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725164", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "4b3283a2-0ab7-41d3-99f2-d9d20bc08319", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "May UNICOM give you instruction regarding circuit joining?", "Answer": "No.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725145", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "8cc9d509-54d7-4b06-ae9c-a8bb9952b931", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725233", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "8cc9d509-54d7-4b06-ae9c-a8bb9952b931", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "What information will UNICOM provide?", "Answer": "Basic weather information, wind, visibility, cloud, temperature, QNH, aerodrome information and conditions, base radio service, telephone service.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725206", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "7f66f6ee-1a97-4224-aa69-369b88454a65", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725297", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "7f66f6ee-1a97-4224-aa69-369b88454a65", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "Where will you find ATIS?", "Answer": "Controlled aerodromes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725277", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "73ac463f-6f6b-44fc-bc4c-960fc4398b8e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725346", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "73ac463f-6f6b-44fc-bc4c-960fc4398b8e", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "What does ATIS stand for?", "Answer": "Automatic Terminal Information Service.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725326", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "51136b33-c43a-4de7-aad7-8812276963c7", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725397", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "51136b33-c43a-4de7-aad7-8812276963c7", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "Where are ATIS frequencies published?", "Answer": "Aerodrome chart, AIPNZ Vol. 4", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725377", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "5e2dc15c-ccef-4534-89d9-6934f38f457d", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725461", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "5e2dc15c-ccef-4534-89d9-6934f38f457d", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "When do you have to listen to ATIS?", "Answer": "Before making initial contact with the applicable ATC.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725440", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "65b1ac04-1a9e-4524-8335-ccbd5e6eea90", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725522", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "65b1ac04-1a9e-4524-8335-ccbd5e6eea90", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "What does AFRU stand for?", "Answer": "Aerodrome frequency response unit.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725502", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "31009455-0dbc-449e-b2ca-5c38c1963080", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725596", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "31009455-0dbc-449e-b2ca-5c38c1963080", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "What is the purpose of the AFRU?", "Answer": "Provides confirmation that pilots are on the correct frequency and that the radio is performing properly.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725563", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "3bedab39-17a1-4ebf-bb43-75a447ce93ef", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725687", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "3bedab39-17a1-4ebf-bb43-75a447ce93ef", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "How will AFRU ensure that the pilot knows if the correct frequency has been selected?", "Answer": "AFRU transmits aerodrome callsign and frequency when there has been no transmissions in a specified time period. (usually 5min)", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725651", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "054f31b1-2882-487b-8a46-01da8050135e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725740", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "054f31b1-2882-487b-8a46-01da8050135e", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "Where will you find AWIB?", "Answer": "Uncontrolled aerodromes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725721", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "e10e4658-86e9-453d-8406-cbe70d437a31", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 5", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725792", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "e10e4658-86e9-453d-8406-cbe70d437a31", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.6", "Question": "Where will you find out how to obtain AWIB information?", "Answer": "Aerodrome chart, AIPNZ Vol. 4", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725771", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "8e5d1f2d-4221-4c15-b2b4-6c814ebf81ec", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "CAR Part 91.217(5)", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725848", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "8e5d1f2d-4221-4c15-b2b4-6c814ebf81ec", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.4", "Question": "Apart from getting NOTAM and weather information before flight, is there any requirement by law to obtain the status of communication facilities to be used?", "Answer": "Yes, under CAR part 91.217(5).", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725825", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "4c669a8f-73bc-4f66-8c9a-4646e01dd75c", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 6", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725926", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "4c669a8f-73bc-4f66-8c9a-4646e01dd75c", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.4", "Question": "When operating as pilot in command in Class C or D airspace, what are the requirements regarding radio communication.", "Answer": "Must maintain two-way radio communication with appropriate ATC on appropriate frequency, unless otherwise authorised.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725884", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "c6ff1280-f2ec-4277-b7ee-b0923c29b55a", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 6", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725983", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c6ff1280-f2ec-4277-b7ee-b0923c29b55a", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.4", "Question": "When operating on the boundary of two different airspaces, the pilot in command of an aircraft may comply with the requirements of which airspace?", "Answer": "The less restrictive airspace.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.725960", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "9dcd4307-d972-4c16-a849-881359f61371", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726051", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "9dcd4307-d972-4c16-a849-881359f61371", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.4", "Question": "An aircraft operating under VFR wishing to communicate with any ATS unit must be equipped with radio equipment that meets what level?", "Answer": "Level 1 or level 2.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726029", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "fc036048-1b9a-49c9-b971-575c34d97fd1", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726114", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "fc036048-1b9a-49c9-b971-575c34d97fd1", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.4", "Question": "What are the requirements regarding radio equipment for an aircraft to operate under VFR in Class B,C,D or Class E airspace at night.", "Answer": "Radio equipment meets level 1 or 2 standards and is capable of providing continuous two-way communications with an appropriate ATC.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726086", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "39bb8aa3-5d3a-42ea-9948-b99b6707f90e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726177", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "39bb8aa3-5d3a-42ea-9948-b99b6707f90e", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.4", "Question": "When operating an aircraft over water under VFR more than 30 minutes flying time from shore, what are the requirements regarding radio equipment?", "Answer": "Radio equipment meets level 1 or 2 standards and is capable of providing continuous two-way communications with an appropriate ATC.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726149", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "b2bd6f5d-bbc9-4424-a76d-59d622591c3d", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726231", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "b2bd6f5d-bbc9-4424-a76d-59d622591c3d", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "HOW DO YOU READ"?\", "Answer": "What is the readability of my transmission?", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726210", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "b66b30d6-d7c7-44d3-8e28-f7e28a33c69d", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726278", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "b66b30d6-d7c7-44d3-8e28-f7e28a33c69d", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": "What does readability 3 mean?", "Answer": "Readable, but with difficulty.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726259", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "bc5e7c05-773d-425b-9ab0-fb7452f75f86", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726327", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "bc5e7c05-773d-425b-9ab0-fb7452f75f86", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": "What does readability 2 mean?", "Answer": "Readable now and then.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726308", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "4274bad7-46c7-4c79-a35c-801367ff9b53", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726375", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "4274bad7-46c7-4c79-a35c-801367ff9b53", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": "What does readability 1 mean?", "Answer": "Unreadable.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726357", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "2abc53fe-1d8d-4bcb-985c-9d0e0dbcb918", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726435", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "2abc53fe-1d8d-4bcb-985c-9d0e0dbcb918", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.2", "Question": "What does readability 4 mean?", "Answer": "Readable.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726416", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "QuestionId": "249b7d61-b762-4351-b2aa-e9e7d179ad4a", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726484", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "249b7d61-b762-4351-b2aa-e9e7d179ad4a", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.", "Question": "What does readability 5 mean?", "Answer": "Perfectly readable.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726465", "Type": "q"}

==========
c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99
2.12 Phraseology and Procedures
==========
{"QuestionId": "249b7d61-b762-4351-b2aa-e9e7d179ad4a", "TopicId": "0be2361d-1e5f-4fd3-a274-55b3fcce731c", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.", "Question": "What does readability 5 mean?", "Answer": "Perfectly readable.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726465", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "e0f1b017-09d0-4afb-9754-bdd01634b048", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726563", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "e0f1b017-09d0-4afb-9754-bdd01634b048", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "ATC advises you of a change in QNH to 995 hPa, how should the QNH be read back?", "Answer": "Niner Niner Fife.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726542", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "c878f879-0b02-4afc-bb5e-ba449e9dd226", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726614", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c878f879-0b02-4afc-bb5e-ba449e9dd226", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you pronounce the following callsign, ANB?", "Answer": "Alfa, November, Bravo.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726594", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "30e3f63b-5310-4a33-9ac4-366ade4abd81", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726664", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "30e3f63b-5310-4a33-9ac4-366ade4abd81", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you phonetically pronounce the callsign OCP?", "Answer": "Oscar, Charlie, Papa.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726645", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "fc2606f3-da06-4b0b-9b06-06d9322f8a71", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726715", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "fc2606f3-da06-4b0b-9b06-06d9322f8a71", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you phonetically pronounce the callsign QRD?", "Answer": "Quebec, Romeo, Delta.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726695", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "2ffe6f97-14da-499d-a858-f128918d6def", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726775", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "2ffe6f97-14da-499d-a858-f128918d6def", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you pronounce the following callsign, ESF?", "Answer": "Echo, Sierra, Foxtrot.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726755", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "51356b67-541a-4f26-8a3b-9f98dd100c54", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726826", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "51356b67-541a-4f26-8a3b-9f98dd100c54", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you pronounce the following callsign, TGU?", "Answer": "Tango, Golf, Uniform.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726807", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "24a7e090-6e52-482a-bd07-74c72561319e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726877", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "24a7e090-6e52-482a-bd07-74c72561319e", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you pronounce the following callsign, HVI?", "Answer": "Hotel, Victor, India.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726858", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "026cd07e-80eb-4842-979a-d39a01829257", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726928", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "026cd07e-80eb-4842-979a-d39a01829257", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you pronounce the following callsign, JWK?", "Answer": "Juliet, Whiskey, Kilo.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726908", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "d0c09c74-b190-4b55-bdad-14b0b7988d40", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726978", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "d0c09c74-b190-4b55-bdad-14b0b7988d40", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you pronounce the following callsign, XLY?", "Answer": "X-Ray, Lima, Yankee.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.726959", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "c1b79cc0-395f-430e-bd06-12362a40b557", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727027", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c1b79cc0-395f-430e-bd06-12362a40b557", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you pronounce the following callsign, YMZ?", "Answer": "Yankee, Mike, Zulu.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727007", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "c60d8755-b774-46b5-b7f4-e227baf93513", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727079", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c60d8755-b774-46b5-b7f4-e227baf93513", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should the following frequency be transmitted, 127.30?", "Answer": "Wun Too Seven Day see mal Tree Zero.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727058", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "040ba00a-83ee-48ea-b6d3-e19ab6df6bc6", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727143", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "040ba00a-83ee-48ea-b6d3-e19ab6df6bc6", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "What does the term \"BREAK BREAK\" mean?", "Answer": "It indicates a separation between messages transmitted to different aircraft.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727121", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "20a602b8-1545-47e7-b835-f1ad13b6789f", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727196", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "20a602b8-1545-47e7-b835-f1ad13b6789f", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "If a previous clearance is no longer applicable, what term will ATC use to indicate this?", "Answer": "CANCEL.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727176", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "64811d9a-a3cf-4166-bb2c-8053ca71e3a4", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727248", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "64811d9a-a3cf-4166-bb2c-8053ca71e3a4", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "What term can ATC use to indicate a separation between portions of a message to an aircraft?", "Answer": "BREAK.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727228", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "c7836a38-e5db-4b46-8de2-de112a3a282e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727301", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c7836a38-e5db-4b46-8de2-de112a3a282e", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "You are at 1200 feet when Tower asks you to report your altitude, how would you", "Answer": "Wun Tousand Too Hundred feet.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727277", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "508847b2-11d8-4094-84de-b670c254a7ea", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727367", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "508847b2-11d8-4094-84de-b670c254a7ea", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "On request, ATC gives you a unique transponder code of 2461, how would you read back this code correctly.", "Answer": "Too Fower Six Wun.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727347", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "d62905fc-46e2-412d-aaf8-f4ca77e39115", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727422", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "d62905fc-46e2-412d-aaf8-f4ca77e39115", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "Just prior to receiving your landing clearance Tower gives you a report of the current wind velocity at 340o 16 kts.  How will they read this to you?", "Answer": "Tree Fower Zero degrees Wun Six knots.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727399", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "d6b00fad-ee4e-4a92-93a2-e06f41fafd22", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727476", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "d6b00fad-ee4e-4a92-93a2-e06f41fafd22", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "The time now is 12:47 and your estimated time of arrival (ETA) at your destination is 13:22.  How will you transmit your ETA?", "Answer": "Too Too next hour.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727455", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "e959efba-c0ea-4d34-8a8d-31ed9c2e320d", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727536", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "e959efba-c0ea-4d34-8a8d-31ed9c2e320d", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "How should you respond to a question if the answer is YES?", "Answer": "AFFIRM.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727517", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "0ffca030-cae3-46f4-964b-0affe37466d4", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727584", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "0ffca030-cae3-46f4-964b-0affe37466d4", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "When communicating with ATC, how should you respond to a question if the answer is NO?", "Answer": "NEGATIVE.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727565", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "f122ae19-2617-4544-8600-345d74a2540e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727651", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "f122ae19-2617-4544-8600-345d74a2540e", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "What does it mean when Tower asks you to \xe2\x80\x98ACKNOWLEDGE\xe2\x80\x99?", "Answer": "Let them know that you have received and understood the message.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727630", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "214c7013-7b09-44f8-a107-9e6d3c32f971", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727708", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "214c7013-7b09-44f8-a107-9e6d3c32f971", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": "With what phrase will ATC reply to grant you permission for an action?", "Answer": "APPROVED.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727689", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "390de764-e82a-4a38-8908-b6ecb929341d", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727756", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "390de764-e82a-4a38-8908-b6ecb929341d", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "CHECK"?\", "Answer": "Examine a system or procedure.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727737", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "2ca8e744-99e9-406e-a8cd-7c9893e993dc", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727804", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "2ca8e744-99e9-406e-a8cd-7c9893e993dc", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "CLEARED"?\", "Answer": "Authorisation under specified conditions.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727785", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "bef2d073-d5bd-458c-8ea6-46249b31f3ac", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727862", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "bef2d073-d5bd-458c-8ea6-46249b31f3ac", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "CONFIRM"?\", "Answer": "Verification of a request.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727832", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "42f9c05d-eb31-4393-a3d4-a763d41bed81", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727926", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "42f9c05d-eb31-4393-a3d4-a763d41bed81", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "CONTACT"?\", "Answer": "To establish communication.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727906", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "624e92d6-5a91-4ab1-86cc-210f7920ccb1", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727974", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "624e92d6-5a91-4ab1-86cc-210f7920ccb1", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "CORRECT"?\", "Answer": "True or accurate.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.727956", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "6979307c-ca69-4b8f-b252-e43b67a3e9b5", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728023", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "6979307c-ca69-4b8f-b252-e43b67a3e9b5", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "CORRECTION"?\", "Answer": "An error has been made and the version follows.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728003", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "cf28df92-beca-4e0b-92e3-b55a3eb349e5", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728069", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "cf28df92-beca-4e0b-92e3-b55a3eb349e5", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "DISREGARD"?\", "Answer": "Ignore.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728052", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "41678e74-150d-4291-9f99-12b65dea70f1", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728115", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "41678e74-150d-4291-9f99-12b65dea70f1", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "GO AHEAD"?\", "Answer": "Proceed with your message.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728097", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "c3ce84d9-b771-475a-bd5f-10cb42f20000", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728164", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c3ce84d9-b771-475a-bd5f-10cb42f20000", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "I SAY AGAIN"?\", "Answer": "I repeat for clarity of emphasis.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728145", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "58ab7f06-269d-4f9b-b67a-b13b329b0f26", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728215", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "58ab7f06-269d-4f9b-b67a-b13b329b0f26", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "MONITOR"?\", "Answer": "Listen out on a specified frequency.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728196", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "8b84c786-49e8-4e5e-b909-7619eb247ed5", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728277", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "8b84c786-49e8-4e5e-b909-7619eb247ed5", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "READ BACK"?\", "Answer": "Repeat the message, or specified part, exactly as received.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728256", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "68bba722-4acf-49c8-b116-41cae58d10f3", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728329", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "68bba722-4acf-49c8-b116-41cae58d10f3", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "RE-CLEARED"?\", "Answer": "A change has been made to your last clearance and this now supersedes your previous clearance.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728307", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "8bce7d0e-5941-4d1b-b92d-cdc943dded74", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728375", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "8bce7d0e-5941-4d1b-b92d-cdc943dded74", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "REPORT"?\", "Answer": "Pass me the specified information.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728357", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "f2fc30c4-6df6-4aae-876f-9485e2e51895", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728423", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "f2fc30c4-6df6-4aae-876f-9485e2e51895", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "REQUEST"?\", "Answer": "I would like to know or, I wish to obtain.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728404", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "8c36449d-06e8-440d-a5c3-69ab4bb2a8c6", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728476", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "8c36449d-06e8-440d-a5c3-69ab4bb2a8c6", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "ROGER"?\", "Answer": "I have received all of your last transmission.  Not to be used as part of a read back or an answer in the affirmative or negative.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728453", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "65cfdd55-e2eb-410e-b3a0-f1d5463c5672", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728526", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "65cfdd55-e2eb-410e-b3a0-f1d5463c5672", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "SAY AGAIN"?\", "Answer": "Repeat all or part (as specified) of your message.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728506", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "7a0b8eff-2514-40da-9b49-f099bec7378e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728573", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "7a0b8eff-2514-40da-9b49-f099bec7378e", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "STANDBY"?\", "Answer": "Wait and I will call you.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728555", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "e8f1e4ff-ba06-485f-8f5e-5d649551365b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728634", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "e8f1e4ff-ba06-485f-8f5e-5d649551365b", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "UNABLE"?\", "Answer": "Unable to comply with request, instruction or clearance.  Normally followed by reason.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728612", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "ec234df5-ff4e-4a22-be32-dda3fb7b4e0c", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728683", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "ec234df5-ff4e-4a22-be32-dda3fb7b4e0c", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "WILCO"?\", "Answer": "I understand your message and will comply.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728664", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "7043174c-bf23-4f1a-9ddf-e590e39c968b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728735", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "7043174c-bf23-4f1a-9ddf-e590e39c968b", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What is meant by the term "WORDS TWICE"?\", "Answer": "Please send every word or group of words twice, or, I am sending every word or group of words twice.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728713", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "00ce04ac-1d77-4a90-a033-729aebac4b2e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728786", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "00ce04ac-1d77-4a90-a033-729aebac4b2e", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"When can we use the term "IMMEDIATE"?\", "Answer": "Only when immediate action is required for reasons of safety.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728766", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "QuestionId": "3693c805-7b30-4fbe-8edf-290deec17e13", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728837", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "3693c805-7b30-4fbe-8edf-290deec17e13", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What does the term "EXPEDITE" mean?\", "Answer": "Proceed as quickly as safely possible", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728815", "Type": "q"}

==========
265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580
2.14 Distress and Urgency Communications
==========
{"QuestionId": "3693c805-7b30-4fbe-8edf-290deec17e13", "TopicId": "c3efc13c-2927-4334-8730-2a48350f7b99", "SyllabusRef": "2.12.2", "Question": \"What does the term "EXPEDITE" mean?\", "Answer": "Proceed as quickly as safely possible", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728815", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "7e919290-a271-4f26-ba19-23f07ef12de1", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728914", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "7e919290-a271-4f26-ba19-23f07ef12de1", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.2", "Question": "In what situation will it be most appropriate to make a MAYDAY call?", "Answer": "Any emergency situation that requires immediate assistance.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728893", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "2028b4ab-40fc-4d3c-8370-c829496cec34", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 2", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728983", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "2028b4ab-40fc-4d3c-8370-c829496cec34", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.2", "Question": "At what level of urgency is it appropriate to make a PAN-PAN call?", "Answer": "In a condition concerning the safety of the aircraft, another aircraft, person on board or in sight, but not requiring immediate assistance.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.728957", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "0bc93f58-8556-4864-8b85-2719a3463824", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729038", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "0bc93f58-8556-4864-8b85-2719a3463824", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.4", "Question": "Which frequencies should you make a MAYDAY call on?", "Answer": "The air-ground frequency in use, an appropriate monitored frequency, or 121.5.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729016", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "32ffe51a-e7f6-449e-a389-6fb5f98b660a", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729090", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "32ffe51a-e7f6-449e-a389-6fb5f98b660a", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.4", "Question": "When making a PAN-PAN call, which frequencies should you use.", "Answer": "The air-ground frequency in use, an appropriate monitored frequency, or 121.5.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729068", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "0799d8ec-5d87-401a-946b-4467622af37e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729137", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "0799d8ec-5d87-401a-946b-4467622af37e", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.4", "Question": "At what pace should you make an emergency transmission?", "Answer": "At a slow deliberate rate.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729118", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "77a1ea1e-2978-428b-9aa3-3fe5ad06df74", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729190", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "77a1ea1e-2978-428b-9aa3-3fe5ad06df74", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.2", "Question": "Total engine failure, structural failure, incapacitation of the pilot, fire or smoke are examples of situations that warrant what type of emergency radio call?", "Answer": "MAYDAY.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729169", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "2b890757-e08a-4bbd-a8c2-f70c08105edd", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729245", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "2b890757-e08a-4bbd-a8c2-f70c08105edd", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.4", "Question": "What is the ideal sequence of a MAYDAY call?", "Answer": "Mayday (spoken three times), name of station addressed, callsign, nature of distress, intentions, position altitude and heading.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729221", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "60ce7a52-74c1-4c1b-a9d1-8f7e8827a420", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729313", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "60ce7a52-74c1-4c1b-a9d1-8f7e8827a420", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.4", "Question": "What is the ideal sequence of a PAN-PAN call?", "Answer": "PAN-PAN (spoken three times), name of station addressed, callsign, nature of urgency, intentions, position altitude and heading, any other useful information.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729286", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "c83cc5d4-e895-4fe5-9696-9069a17a919b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729373", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c83cc5d4-e895-4fe5-9696-9069a17a919b", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.4", "Question": "On hearing a distress message broadcast on the frequency you have set at the time, what do you need to do?", "Answer": "Maintain radio silence and a listening watch on the frequency until satisfactory assistance is established.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729345", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "QuestionId": "298ed276-518f-45d6-b074-742f9d479881", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 7", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729425", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "298ed276-518f-45d6-b074-742f9d479881", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.6", "Question": "As the pilot in command of an aircraft responding to a distress call in the absence of ATS, are you allowed to impose radio silence on other aircraft.", "Answer": "Yes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729404", "Type": "q"}

==========
6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c
2.16 Loss of Communication – Aircraft Equipment
==========
{"QuestionId": "298ed276-518f-45d6-b074-742f9d479881", "TopicId": "265eb441-89b6-47b5-9b16-c3f0b7629580", "SyllabusRef": "2.14.6", "Question": "As the pilot in command of an aircraft responding to a distress call in the absence of ATS, are you allowed to impose radio silence on other aircraft.", "Answer": "Yes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729404", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "131480fe-8f51-477d-a096-ab2813a2deb9", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 1", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729512", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "131480fe-8f51-477d-a096-ab2813a2deb9", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.2", "Question": "On first encountering a suspected radio failure, how would you check the radio power sources?", "Answer": "Check that the master switch and/or avionics master switch (if fitted) is ON, and check that the radio ON/OFF switch is ON, lastly check the circuit breaker.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729484", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "cdcd2e5d-0426-426b-97db-9f84e8add851", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729566", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "cdcd2e5d-0426-426b-97db-9f84e8add851", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.", "Question": "Troubleshooting the radio function settings following a suspected radio failure, what should be checked?", "Answer": "Squelch not set too low, correct frequency set and volume at audible level.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729544", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "a814d9e4-e438-4f29-bb30-8915048892eb", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729634", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "a814d9e4-e438-4f29-bb30-8915048892eb", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.2", "Question": "On suspecting a radio failure, how can you be sure that it is not the microphone or headset that is at fault?", "Answer": "If using a headset and boom microphone, switch to the cockpit speaker and hand held microphone or vice versa.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729609", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "d7ae022b-6b10-40ab-b80f-5b313664d482", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729703", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "d7ae022b-6b10-40ab-b80f-5b313664d482", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.4", "Question": "What actions should you take in the event of a communications failure in controlled airspace?", "Answer": "Continue as last cleared, and avoiding high traffic density, divert to a suitable unattended aerodrome.  If unable to divert, make an overhead join no lower than 1500 feet AGL.  Follow communications failure procedures as published in AIPNZ Vol 4 AD chart.  Squawk 7600.  Listen to ATIS.  Use a mobile phone if available to contact ATS.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729664", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "a850ac9d-0956-4335-871f-6ee83fd86421", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729762", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "a850ac9d-0956-4335-871f-6ee83fd86421", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.4", "Question": "What actions should you take in the event of a communications failure in uncontrolled airspace?", "Answer": "Remain clear of controlled airspace and land at the nearest suitable aerodrome.  Use a mobile phone if available to contact ATS.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729736", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "6fe60fae-204d-4588-b8be-e74b4128429d", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729820", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "6fe60fae-204d-4588-b8be-e74b4128429d", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.4", "Question": "What action should you take if experiencing a communications failure in an MBZ?", "Answer": "Divert to an aerodrome outside of the MBZ unless the situation demands remaining in the MBZ.  Use a mobile phone if available to contact ATS.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729794", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "daeef94c-4191-405b-8fe3-69f79863bc83", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729882", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "daeef94c-4191-405b-8fe3-69f79863bc83", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.6", "Question": "What are the corrective actions should be taken with regard to the frequency set on the radio in the event of a communications failure.", "Answer": "Change the frequency to the alternate for the applicable station (if available), or change the frequency to another station within VHF range.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729855", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "5f34c487-98e0-49a4-9429-ed8d9857ab89", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729954", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "5f34c487-98e0-49a4-9429-ed8d9857ab89", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.6", "Question": "What actions should you take if you are experiencing  a communications failure and you are certain that the receiver is unserviceable but the transmitter might be working?", "Answer": "Make radio calls as required, prefixing each call with the words \xe2\x80\x98TRANSMITTING BLIND\xe2\x80\x99.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729927", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "80e15c1e-edbf-4651-9cc6-fd32de85e1cf", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730012", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "80e15c1e-edbf-4651-9cc6-fd32de85e1cf", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.6", "Question": "What actions could you take if you are flying through mountainous terrain and you are having difficulty establishing communications even though your radio is serviceable?", "Answer": "Climb to a higher altitude to increase the range of your radio.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.729988", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "3a698f4f-d661-4a6c-b8d2-0f705b76c73b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730065", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "3a698f4f-d661-4a6c-b8d2-0f705b76c73b", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.8", "Question": "How should you reply YES (affirmative) to a question from ATC if you are using the speechless technique?", "Answer": \"Activate the "push to talk" once.\", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730044", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "f7488bb8-d0a1-4a35-889d-3be8b7ffc671", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730117", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "f7488bb8-d0a1-4a35-889d-3be8b7ffc671", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.8", "Question": "How should you reply NO (negative) to a question from ATC if you are using the speechless technique?", "Answer": "Activate the transmitter two times.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730096", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "d8768c36-512c-40be-a0cd-828914b31d83", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730168", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "d8768c36-512c-40be-a0cd-828914b31d83", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.8", "Question": "How should you ask ATC to repeat their last transmission if you are using the speechless technique?", "Answer": "Activate the transmitter three times.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730147", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "858f2e4d-ce80-492f-875e-c02043a39010", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730223", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "858f2e4d-ce80-492f-875e-c02043a39010", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.8", "Question": "ATC have cleared you to track to and report at a certain position, how will you let them know that you have reached this point using the speechless technique?", "Answer": "Activate the transmitter four times.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730200", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "d6c36181-c633-41f5-8c4e-3987ee8b6710", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730285", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "d6c36181-c633-41f5-8c4e-3987ee8b6710", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "In the event of a comms failure in controlled airspace, how will the control tower indicate that you are cleared to land?", "Answer": "By signalling a steady green light.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730263", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "1c18b535-c645-4cd3-bda6-43c7e86af223", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730338", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "1c18b535-c645-4cd3-bda6-43c7e86af223", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "In the event of a comms failure, how will the control tower indicate that you are cleared for takeoff?", "Answer": "By signalling a steady green light.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730317", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "31fc405b-c6db-4bce-bc4f-1da183fb969b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730407", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "31fc405b-c6db-4bce-bc4f-1da183fb969b", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "What does a steady red light signal from the control tower indicate if you are airborne?", "Answer": "Give way to other aircraft and continue circuiting.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730381", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "9acfa336-48d6-4ce5-a098-06402a4c82a1", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730458", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "9acfa336-48d6-4ce5-a098-06402a4c82a1", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "What do you have to do if you see a steady red light signal shown to you by the control tower while you are on the ground?", "Answer": "Stop.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730439", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "9d13cd5f-43d8-4696-b5a4-b3363a89266b", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730511", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "9d13cd5f-43d8-4696-b5a4-b3363a89266b", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "While experiencing a radio failure in the circuit at a controlled aerodrome, the control tower signals you with a series of green flashes.  What do you need to do?", "Answer": "Return for landing.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730490", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "840a9404-0c40-4361-ad28-6863c2027882", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730561", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "840a9404-0c40-4361-ad28-6863c2027882", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "While holding prior to taxiing to the runway, the control tower sends you a series of green flashes with a signal light.  What does this mean?", "Answer": "You are now cleared to taxi.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730540", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "304e6aca-f52a-4b56-b06d-984a487a3617", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730616", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "304e6aca-f52a-4b56-b06d-984a487a3617", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "You are approaching a controlled aerodrome, unable to establish radio communication, when you see a series of red flashes from the control tower.  What does this mean?", "Answer": "The aerodrome is unsafe \xe2\x80\x93 do not land.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730593", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "73eba824-fd3c-4c86-896a-8bd780e486e6", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730677", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "73eba824-fd3c-4c86-896a-8bd780e486e6", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "What do a series of red flashes from the control tower mean?", "Answer": "Taxi clear of the landing area.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730657", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "65213578-9826-49df-a05a-84be7180bfc8", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730725", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "65213578-9826-49df-a05a-84be7180bfc8", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "What do a series of white flashes from the control tower mean?", "Answer": "Land this aerodrome and proceed to the apron.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730706", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "4a4bba1a-5743-4ea1-8106-7340b3f34c08", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730775", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "4a4bba1a-5743-4ea1-8106-7340b3f34c08", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "What does a series of white flashes from the tower mean while you are holding on the taxiway?", "Answer": "Return to starting point on the aerodrome.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730755", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "e938200f-e6d0-4d9b-9d9e-1e7fbd17d29a", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730823", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "e938200f-e6d0-4d9b-9d9e-1e7fbd17d29a", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.10.10", "Question": "As you turn on to final approach what does a series of red and green flashes from the control tower mean?", "Answer": "Danger \xe2\x80\x93 be on alert.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730803", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "a2553c12-380b-41f9-9678-027afa4804f8", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730877", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "a2553c12-380b-41f9-9678-027afa4804f8", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "While getting ready to leave the fuel pumps you are unable to raise the control tower on the radio, but you see a series of alternating red and green flashes.  What does this mean?", "Answer": "Danger \xe2\x80\x93 be on alert.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730855", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "QuestionId": "6fd6774a-a387-4bf0-961d-b8ab896668e7", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730930", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "6fd6774a-a387-4bf0-961d-b8ab896668e7", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "If at any time in flight around an aerodrome you see a red pyrotechnic, what does this mean?", "Answer": "Notwithstanding any previous instructions, do not land for the time being.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730908", "Type": "q"}

==========
607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0
2.18 Loss of Communication – ATS Equipment Failure
==========
{"QuestionId": "6fd6774a-a387-4bf0-961d-b8ab896668e7", "TopicId": "6d8fefc4-fa87-4c61-b8db-8e2edf6dba8c", "SyllabusRef": "2.16.10", "Question": "If at any time in flight around an aerodrome you see a red pyrotechnic, what does this mean?", "Answer": "Notwithstanding any previous instructions, do not land for the time being.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730908", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "QuestionId": "c815665b-a837-4b35-b7c9-c15dc309321a", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731019", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c815665b-a837-4b35-b7c9-c15dc309321a", "TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "SyllabusRef": "2.18.2", "Question": "When will TIBA (Traffic Information Broadcast by Aircraft) be introduced?", "Answer": "If significant disruption to ATC or related services occur.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.730998", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "QuestionId": "247e4fd4-aff5-486b-837a-2049c2b0cb38", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731071", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "247e4fd4-aff5-486b-837a-2049c2b0cb38", "TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "SyllabusRef": "2.18.4", "Question": "What are the frequencies for TIBA?", "Answer": "Unless otherwise notified by NOTAM, use the frequency normally used for that airspace.  A TIBA NOTAM will advise the frequency to be used.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731046", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "QuestionId": "0ad7aee5-ea6d-412b-95eb-a7366d425d46", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731132", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "0ad7aee5-ea6d-412b-95eb-a7366d425d46", "TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "SyllabusRef": "2.18.4", "Question": "You are approaching airspace which has a different frequency to what you have set on your radio.  Under TIBA procedures, what is the requirement for maintaining a listening watch on the new frequency?", "Answer": "You should be maintaining a listening watch on the appropriate frequency ten minutes before entering the airspace, until leaving the airspace.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731104", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "QuestionId": "ea40f47b-2a43-4895-bfe9-f646b617fc97", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731182", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "ea40f47b-2a43-4895-bfe9-f646b617fc97", "TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "SyllabusRef": "2.18.4", "Question": "Under TIBA procedures when should you be making broadcasts on takeoff?", "Answer": "As soon as possible before or after takeoff.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731163", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "QuestionId": "98abb890-0823-4a19-80e3-392d615ff398", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731233", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "98abb890-0823-4a19-80e3-392d615ff398", "TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "SyllabusRef": "2.18.4", "Question": "If TIBA procedures are in effect, when should you be making broadcasts when entering airspace?", "Answer": "Ten minutes before entering designated airspace?", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731212", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "QuestionId": "87bf7318-bbbe-43fb-96d1-9b75efb9076e", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731291", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "87bf7318-bbbe-43fb-96d1-9b75efb9076e", "TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "SyllabusRef": "2.18.4", "Question": "When should you be making TIBA broadcasts nearing a reporting point?", "Answer": "Crossing a reporting point.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731272", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "QuestionId": "c150a5cb-3e48-4569-a5ca-ba7ab4f5f143", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731344", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "c150a5cb-3e48-4569-a5ca-ba7ab4f5f143", "TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "SyllabusRef": "2.18.4", "Question": "With regard to changing altitude while TIBA procedures are in effect, when should you make broadcasts?", "Answer": "2 to 5 minutes before changing altitude, at the time of changing altitude, and on reaching the required altitude.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731320", "Type": "q"}

{"TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "QuestionId": "cdf82a86-0900-473c-874f-22314ec70cc4", "Url": "https://www.waypoints.nz/products/vol-04-flight-radio-for-pilots-july-2016", "Text": "Waypoints Volume 4 Chapter 3", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731393", "Type": "r"}

{"QuestionId": "cdf82a86-0900-473c-874f-22314ec70cc4", "TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "SyllabusRef": "2.18.4", "Question": "Are you allowed to make broadcasts under TIBA procedures whenever you consider it necessary?", "Answer": "Yes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731375", "Type": "q"}

{"QuestionId": "cdf82a86-0900-473c-874f-22314ec70cc4", "TopicId": "607b7e2f-131e-4f60-9843-ada5deb909f0", "SyllabusRef": "2.18.4", "Question": "Are you allowed to make broadcasts under TIBA procedures whenever you consider it necessary?", "Answer": "Yes.", "AddedDate": "2019-03-22 14:33:56.731375", "Type": "q"}

